export interface Question {
  question: string;
  answer: string;
}
export interface QuestionList {
  [date: string]: Question[];
}

export const ClassroomQuestions: QuestionList = {
  "4/12": [
    {
      question: "Tell me what the Devil’s Dictionary defines as the Hider factor in the progress of the human race.",
      answer: "Villains",
    },
  ],
  "4/19": [
    {
      question: "Between A and B ... which line seems longer ...?",
      answer: "They’re the same",
    },
  ],
  "4/23": [
    {
      question: "Between music, theater, and chariot racing, which sport did Nero win when he participated in the Olympics?",
      answer: "All of them",
    },
  ],
  "4/25": [
    {
      question: 'What does the phrase "My country right or wrong" mean to convey?',
      answer: "You unquestionably support it",
    },
    {
      question: "But the original meaning was different? So I guess it'd be something like...",
      answer: "You have a duty to correct it",
    },
  ],
  "4/27": [
    {
      question: "Do you know the name of the theorem named after this number?",
      answer: "Four color theorem",
    },
  ],
  "4/30": [
    {
      question: 'First off, the "wunder" part probably means ...?',
      answer: "Wonder",
    },
    {
      question: 'Next, the "kind" part. That’s probably ...',
      answer: "Child",
    },
    {
      question: 'Yeah, that’s gotta be it. "Kind" means a child ... or at least a young guy, in your case',
      answer: "A prodigy",
    },
  ],
  "5/7": [
    {
      question: 'So what’s the literal translation of the phrase "femme fatale?"',
      answer: "Fatal woman",
    },
  ],
  "5/10": [
    {
      question: "You know the time period Yoshitsune was active in, don’t you?",
      answer: "The Heian period",
    },
  ],
  "5/11": [
    {
      question: 'What historical figure inspired "favoring the magistrate?"',
      answer: "Minamoto no Yoshitsune",
    },
    {
      question: "Yoshitune had a brother, right. Oh, I think his name was ...",
      answer: "Minamoto no Yoritomo",
    },
    {
      question: "But they ended up coming into conflict. And in the end when they had to oppose each other ...",
      answer: "Yoritomo won",
    },
    {
      question: "That’s probably because people tend to sympathize less with people in power, and sympathize more with ...",
      answer: "The weak",
    },
  ],
  "5/12": [
    {
      question: "Which brain function is responsible for the phenomenon of seeing an illusion in this figure?",
      answer: "Cognition",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following maps can you paint without any adjacent areas being the same color?",
      answer: "Both",
    },
  ],
  "5/13": [
    {
      question: 'Name that book that defined "male factor" as the chief factor in the progress of the human race.',
      answer: "The Devil’s Dictionary",
    },
    {
      question: "What character archetype refers to a mysterious and seductive woman, typically with ulterior motives?",
      answer: "Femme Fatale",
    },
  ],
  "5/16": [
    {
      question: "What do we call the phenomenon where believing in a treatment’s power is enough to improve your condition?",
      answer: "The Placebo effect",
    },
  ],
  "5/19": [
    {
      question: "Which famous artist of the Edo period is said to have moved residence over 100 times?",
      answer: "Katsushika Hokusai",
    },
  ],
  "5/21": [
    {
      question: "The golden ratio is 1:1.618 but do you know the silver ratio?",
      answer: "1:1.414",
    },
  ],
  "5/23": [
    {
      question: 'If we think about what these words have in common, then maybe "syn" means ...',
      answer: "Together",
    },
    {
      question: 'And "aisthesis," huh? That’s a little like the word aesthetics. I wonder if it means ...',
      answer: "Senses",
    },
    {
      question: "So that means the full word basically means...",
      answer: "Senses coming together",
    },
  ],
  "5/26": [
    {
      question: "Do you know which author Leblanc borrowed from?",
      answer: "Arthur Conan Doyle",
    },
  ],
  "5/31": [
    {
      question: "Do you know which peg-legged, parrot toting historical figure’s appearance became visual shorthand for pirates?",
      answer: "John Silver",
    },
  ],
  "6/4": [
    {
      question: "What do you think the name for the phenomenon is?",
      answer: "The halo effect",
    },
  ],
  "6/7": [
    {
      question: "The red king crab is biologically related to the hermit crab. So how is it different from a crab. Do you know?",
      answer: "The number of legs",
    },
  ],
  "6/8": [
    {
      question: "Where does totalitarianism take things a step further than authoritarianism?",
      answer: "Controlling Public Thought",
    },
  ],
  "6/13": [
    {
      question: "What color do you think it turns (when washing your hair with copper)",
      answer: "Green",
    },
  ],
  "6/15": [
    {
      question: "Between paper bills and coins, which one is issued by the government?",
      answer: "Coins",
    },
  ],
  "6/20": [
    {
      question: "One of these has minor metals in it, right?",
      answer: "Smartphone",
    },
  ],
  "6/23": [
    {
      question: "Now do you know what this woman’s position was?",
      answer: "A pope",
    },
  ],
  "6/27": [
    {
      question: "Which of these animals is involved in an English idiom about the weather?",
      answer: "Dogs",
    },
  ],
  "6/29": [
    {
      question: "What do you think it says on the back of this (Shogi) piece?",
      answer: "Gold",
    },
  ],
  "7/1": [
    {
      question: "What’s the meaning of the original Chinese phrase that these dumplings’ name came from?",
      answer: "Barbarian’s Head",
    },
  ],
  "7/4": [
    {
      question: "Two people are responsible for July and August having 31 days. Do you know who those people are?",
      answer: "Julius and Augustus",
    },
  ],
  "7/7": [
    {
      question: "So Tanabata’s about gods crossing a starry sky to reunite once every year. It might have something to do with... ?",
      answer: "The Milky Way",
    },
    {
      question: "Traditional food",
      answer: "Soumen’s noodles",
    },
  ],
  "7/9": [
    {
      question: "Do you know what shape it is?",
      answer: "A triangle",
    },
  ],
  "7/11": [
    {
      question: "What is long-term memory, anyway?",
      answer: "Memories that last a long time",
    },
    {
      question: "Markus mentioned something about the amount of memories you could store, right? Something like ...",
      answer: "Infinite",
    },
    {
      question: "If you have theoretically infinite space for them... Theoretically, you’d be able to retain them for ...",
      answer: "Forever",
    },
  ],
  "7/12": [
    {
      question: "Do you know what he did?",
      answer: "Thievery",
    },
  ],
  "7/13": [
    {
      question: "If angle C is 28 degrees, and angles A and D are 88 degrees, what is the angle of B and E?",
      answer: "64 degrees",
    },
    {
      question: "I think this came up in class. They were invented by the campus’s guy from Romance of the Three Kingdoms, right?",
      answer: "Zhuge Liang",
    },
    {
      question: "And they were offering something to quell the river ...",
      answer: "Barbarians’ heads",
    },
    {
      question: "This master strategist came up with the baozi to",
      answer: "To offer them instead of heads",
    },
  ],
  "7/14": [
    {
      question: "What is the name and genus of this organism?",
      answer: "Red King Crab (Paralithodes)",
    },
    {
      question: "What happened when the government issued paper and hard currencies in Japan for the first time?",
      answer: "It caused confusion in the economy",
    },
  ],
  "7/15": [
    {
      question: 'What is the English equivalent of the Norwegian idiom "raining witches?"',
      answer: "Raining cats and dogs",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is another name for spikenard noodles traditionally eaten in Tanabata?",
      answer: "Demon guts",
    },
  ],
  "9/3": [
    {
      question: "Each hand in this famous statue means something, but ... do you know what the right represents?",
      answer: "Prosperity",
    },
  ],
  "9/6": [
    {
      question: "Do you know the name of that phenomenon where the second hand looks like it’s stopped moving?",
      answer: "Chronostasis",
    },
  ],
  "9/14": [
    {
      question: "What does a pawn shop offer that a secondhand shop doesn’t?",
      answer: "Money loans for collateral",
    },
  ],
  "9/17": [
    {
      question: 'What’s one of the supposed origins for the phrase "cat got your tongue?"',
      answer: "Cats eating human tongues",
    },
  ],
  "9/21": [
    {
      question: "Robot comes from a word in Czech ... but where in Europe is the Czech Republic located?",
      answer: "Central Europe",
    },
  ],
  "9/24": [
    {
      question: "How many white and black shapes are there respectively on a soccer ball?",
      answer: "20 white, 12 black",
    },
  ],
  "9/28": [
    {
      question: 'So "PVS," referring to when you mistakenly think your phone is going off... What\'s the P?',
      answer: "Phantom",
    },
    {
      question: 'The next part is the V part. That means it\'d be "phantom..." what?',
      answer: "Vibration",
    },
    {
      question: 'Last is the S. So if we have "phantom vibration" so far...?',
      answer: "Syndrome",
    },
  ],
  "9/29": [
    {
      question: "But the fishermen of Nagaragawa are actually civil servants as well. So, tell me which sector they belong to.",
      answer: "Imperial Household Agency",
    },
  ],
  "10/3": [
    {
      question: 'If we use "three watermelons in the sun" to visualize a certain matter’s size against the universe’s, what are the melons?',
      answer: "Stars",
    },
  ],
  "10/6": [
    {
      question: "Now, do you know who invented this instrument? (Guillotine)",
      answer: "Joseph-Ignace Guillotine",
    },
  ],
  "10/11": [
    {
      question: "Which name was most commonly ascribed to shape B?",
      answer: "Bouba",
    },
  ],
  "10/17": [
    {
      question: "Counting both black and white surfaces, how many surfaces are there in total on a soccer ball?",
      answer: "32 surfaces",
    },
    {
      question: "Didn’t the teacher say that the number of colors used to be different? Do you remember?",
      answer: "It used to be one color",
    },
    {
      question: "Oh yeah, I remember. I think she said that unlike now, soccer games were broadcast with ...",
      answer: "Black and white picture",
    },
  ],
  "10/18": [
    {
      question: "Who conducted executions using this device?",
      answer: "Charles-Henri Sanson",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the reason that most people can not become a commercial fisherman of Nagarasawa?",
      answer: "It’s a hereditary profession",
    },
  ],
  "10/19": [
    {
      question: 'What is the meaning of "robota," the etymological root of "robot"?',
      answer: "Slave labor",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following describes the density of the stars in outer space?",
      answer: "3 bees in all of Europe",
    },
  ],
  "10/22": [
    {
      question: "Now, tell me the total count for each column in this magic square.",
      answer: "15",
    },
  ],
  "10/24": [
    {
      question: "From a psychological standpoint, what’s a key reason our memories can differ from reality?",
      answer: "Memory Bias",
    },
  ],
  "11/2": [
    {
      question: 'Can you tell me the meaning of the word "wack" in Thieves’ Cant?',
      answer: "A share of stolen goods",
    },
  ],
  "11/4": [
    {
      question: "Clubs is a club, diamond is a gem, so what does a spade represent?",
      answer: "A sword",
    },
  ],
  "11/8": [
    {
      question: "Tell me how old you have to be to listen in on a trial?",
      answer: "Any age",
    },
  ],
  "11/10": [
    {
      question: "Do you know why it’s missing in the character for crow?",
      answer: "Crow eyes are hard to see",
    },
  ],
  "11/12": [
    {
      question: "I wonder. Do you know why voices sound so different over the phone?",
      answer: "Because the voice is synthetic.",
    },
  ],
  "11/14": [
    {
      question: "Tell me why that is? (Sun rising over Mt. Fuji)",
      answer: "Because of high altitude",
    },
  ],
  "11/15": [
    {
      question: "He was to be paraded through the city and punished in a very particular way. How was he punished? (Nezumi Kozo)",
      answer: "His head was put on display",
    },
  ],
  "11/17": [
    {
      question: 'Do you know the name for this graph? Your hint is "snails" ...',
      answer: "Cochleoid",
    },
  ],
  "12/20": [
    {
      question: "Choose the graph which is named after the Chinese yoyo known as a diabolo.",
      answer: "D",
    },
    {
      question: "He was a really famous thief in the Edo period, right? How much money did he steal, in the end?",
      answer: "Over one billion yen",
    },
    {
      question: "As a result he was sentenced to ...",
      answer: "Having his head displayed",
    },
    {
      question: "Criminals, especially famous criminals, were mostly parades around for ...",
      answer: "A performance",
    },
  ],
  "12/21": [
    {
      question: "Which suit of cards represents the Holy Grail?",
      answer: "Hearts",
    },
    {
      question: "According to Japanese judicial law, what is possible for even an infant to do in court?",
      answer: "Attend",
    },
  ],
  "12/22": [
    {
      question: 'What country refers to a person who controls politics behind the scenes as a "prime minister in black?"',
      answer: "Japan",
    },
    {
      question: 'The Japanese word "dokyuu" translates to "massive." What English word inspired the initial "do" in dokyuu?',
      answer: "Dreadnought",
    },
  ],
  "1/11": [
    {
      question: "What’s this phrase supposed to illustrate about the gods of Shinto?",
      answer: "How numerous they are",
    },
    {
      question: "What’s the phrase again? The one about how many gods there are in Shinto?",
      answer: "The Eight Million Gods",
    },
  ],
  "1/14": [
    {
      question: 'Where do you think the fictional land of "Ihatov" is modeled after?',
      answer: "Iwate",
    },
  ],
  "1/18": [
    {
      question: "What did the word awful originally mean?",
      answer: "Impressive",
    },
  ],
  "1/20": [
    {
      question: "Do you know what she’s stepping on?",
      answer: "A snake",
    },
  ],
  "1/24": [
    {
      question: "What does that mean when describing a person? (Sweet)",
      answer: "Kind-hearted",
    },
    {
      question: 'So what kind of connotation would "salty" have in that context?',
      answer: "Negative",
    },
    {
      question: 'So with all of that in mind, "salty" probably means ...',
      answer: "Resentful",
    },
  ],
  "1/27": [
    {
      question: "How far did this study suggest personal happiness can spread?",
      answer: "To friends of friends of friends",
    },
  ],
};
